Every developer knows this feeling.
You ship a feature, users love it, and then the support ticket start.
How do I use this? Where's the documentation?
You look at your help docs. They're six months out of date.
Here's the thing. We all know documentation matters, but nobody wants to write it,
so we don't, and our users suffer.
What if your documentation wrote itself?
This is supportpages.io. You connect your GitHub repo just like that,
and our AI reads your entire code base. It understands your product, your features, your users.
Now watch what happens. You merge a pull request.
Instantly, supportpages analyzes the change, not what code changed, what changed for your users,
and it writes a help article, a real one, with steps, with screenshots, ready to publish.
You review it. One click to approve, one click to publish, done.
Your documentation is now always up to date. Every feature, every update, automatically.
And your users, they get a beautiful help center, with search, with AI chat that actually answers their questions.
No more writing docs at midnight. No more. We'll update that later.
No more frustrated users. You ship code. We ship the docs.
That supportpages.io.